http://www.lbfoster.com/en/privacy-policy

Home
Corporate
Chemtec Energy ServicesFriction ManagementPiling, Bridge Products, & ConcreteRail BusinessTubular and Energy Services
About HistoryBusiness SystemOur BrandsLeadershipCorporate ResponsibilityProducts and Solutions Rail BusinessPiling, Bridge Products, & Concrete ProductsTubular & Energy ServicesCareers News SubscribeMomentumContact Investor Relations Sustainability EHSS ProgramEmployee & Human RightsVendor Relations
En
En
Infrastructure SolutionsLegal Disclaimer
Legal Disclaimer
Copyright© 2017.  L.B. Foster® Company.  All Rights Reserved.
Legal Disclaimer
L.B. Foster strives to ensure that the information contained in this Web Site is accurate and reliable. However, due to the possible input and transmission errors and/or unauthorized editing, the Company does not warrant the completeness, timeliness or accuracy of the information presented and you should be aware that the information contained on our Web Site may be incomplete, may contain errors or may have become out-of-date. In particular, the reports filed by L.B. Foster with the Securities and Exchange Commission and listed on this website speak only as of the respective dates on which they were filed or used by L.B. Foster. The contents of those reports may become out-of-date. L.B. Foster makes no commitment, and disclaims any duty, to update any of those reports.
L.B. Foster may periodically revise the information contained in this Web Site and reserves the right to make such changes at any time without any obligation to notify past, current or prospective visitors. In no event shall L.B. Foster be liable for any damages, whether direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages, arising out of any use of the information contained herein.
This Web Site contains links to third-party sites which are not under the control of L.B. Foster. L.B. Foster is not responsible for the content of such third-party web sites. Accordingly, when you access a linked third-party web site, you do so at your own risk and L.B. Foster assumes no responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of any information on these sites.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. We know that maintaining your trust requires that we protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices that you, as a visitor to this site, can make about the collection and use of your information.
Personal Information
When you visit our website, we only collect personal information from you (such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc.) if you voluntarily provide it to us. Depending on the purpose for which the information was provided, we may use the information to communicate with you regarding our services. We will not send you any news or information unless you expressly consent to receive such a communication from us. And if you do choose to receive any such communication from us, you will always have the opportunity to "unsubscribe" from receiving the notification at any time.
Sharing your Personal Information
We will not share your personal information with other companies or organizations, with the possible exception of L.B. Foster’s affiliated entities. We reserve the right to disclose any personal information as needed if such information is requested by law enforcement agencies or if we are required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, court order, or by a government entity.
